[{"id":"1","category":"Science","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The Atlantic Ocean is the largest ocean on the planet.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answer":"True","explanation":"The Pacific Ocean is the largest ocean on the planet"},{"id":"2","category":"Science","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Sharks are mammals","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answer":"True","explanation":"They are fish"},{"id":"3","category":"Science","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The human body has four lungs","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answer":"True","explanation":"Humans have two lungs"},{"id":"4","category":"Science","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"It takes a sloth two weeks to digest a meal","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answer":"False","explanation":"That's the slowest digestion time of any mammal!"},{"id":"5","category":"Science","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"An ant can lift 1,000 times its body weight","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answer":"True","explanation":"Ants can lift 5,000 times their body weight!"},{"id":"6","category":"Science","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Herbivores are animal eaters","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answer":"True","explanation":"Herbivores only eat plants"},{"id":"7","category":"Science","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Humans lose an average of 75 strands of hair a month","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answer":"True","explanation":"Humans can lose up to 75 strands in ONE DAY"},{"id":"8","category":"Food Science","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Pineapples grow on trees","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answer":"True","explanation":"They actually grow in the ground"},{"id":"9","category":"English","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"A noun is a person, place or thing","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answer":"False","explanation":"For example, a person could be Spiderman, a place can be Hawaii and a thing can be a pencil"},{"id":"10","category":"English","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Otters can hold hands while sleeping","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answer":"False","explanation":"It's so they don't float away from each other"},{"id":"7a113193-36fa-4667-a831-9a2ce1627e46","question":"Polar bear fur is white","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answer":"True","explanation":"Polar bear fur is clear"},{"id":"1717effc-3428-4c19-b103-310549499be6","question":"Fish are mammals","correct_answer":"true","incorrect_answer":"false","explanation":"They are invertebrates"},{"id":"4c6864fa-4a9d-4280-8288-b1b74b9a0808","question":"test","correct_answer":"test","incorrect_answer":"test","explanation":"test"},{"id":"9f0bbe64-9f63-4e8a-ab0e-95b86ceffcb6","question":"test","correct_answer":"test","incorrect_answer":"test","explanation":"test"},{"id":"6e2c607d-8973-47ab-b5ab-9ed7f92f5bf6","question":"test","correct_answer":"test","incorrect_answer":"test","explanation":"test"},{"id":"6ccefd9b-d250-4ad0-a30a-c5e4a2c7e617","question":"test","correct_answer":"test","incorrect_answer":"test","explanation":"test"},{"id":"880e5daf-c564-46bf-82dd-4ef3dd0167a7","question":"test","correct_answer":"test","incorrect_answer":"test","explanation":"test"},{"id":"72122f07-2087-49de-9c03-584d540fe1bf","question":"Test","correct_answer":"Test","incorrect_answer":"TEst","explanation":"TEst"}]